blackbottom.com 2012-06-14

# BlackBottom.com Privacy Statement

### Updated as of August 15, 2008

The [BlackBottom.com Privacy Policy](http://www.blackbottom.com/privacy.html) describes how BlackBottom.com and its subsidiaries treat personal information when you use BlackBottom.com services, including information provided when you use BlackBottom.com. In addition, the following describes privacy practices specific to BlackBottom.com. To understand how we treat the information you give us as you use BlackBottom.com, you should read this policy and the BlackBottom.com Privacy Policy.

### Personal Information

  * **Non-Account Activity.** You can watch videos on BlackBottom.com without having a BlackBottom.com Account or a BlackBottom.com Account. You can also contact us about a particular video without having a BlackBottom.com Account or a BlackBottom.com Account.
  * **Account-Related Activity.** Certain other activities on BlackBottom.com—like uploading videos, posting comments, or watching restricted videos—require you to have a BlackBottom.com Account or a BlackBottom.com Account. We ask for some personal information when you create a BlackBottom.com Account or a BlackBottom.com Account, including your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access. A BlackBottom.com Account allows you to access many of our services that require registration.
  * **Usage Information.** We may record information about your usage, such as when you use BlackBottom.com, the channels, groups, and favorites you subscribe to, the contacts you communicate with, the videos you watch, and the frequency and size of data transfers, as well as information you display or click on in BlackBottom.com (including UI elements, settings, and other information). If you are logged in, we may associate that information with your account. We may use clear GIFs (a.k.a. "Web Beacons") in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients.
  * **Content Uploaded to Site.** Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your playback or profile pages, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others.

### Uses

  * If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the BlackBottom.com Sites, we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the general and personalized features and functionality of the BlackBottom.com Sites, and to process any flagging activity or correspondence you send to us.
  * Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other Users when you upload videos or send messages through the BlackBottom.com Sites and other Users can contact you through messages and comments. Any videos that you submit to the BlackBottom.com Sites may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. If you have enabled Active Sharing, other users may see that you, as identified by your account name (not your email address), are watching the same video.
  * We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major BlackBottom.com Site changes or for customer service purposes).
  * We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous user usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the BlackBottom.com Sites and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, analyzing, and processing user preferences and trends, as well as user activity and communications.
  * We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) store information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the BlackBottom.com Sites; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests.

### Your Choices

  * You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the BlackBottom.com Sites, in which case you can still view videos and explore the BlackBottom.com Sites, but BlackBottom.com may not be able to provide certain services to you. Some advanced BlackBottom.com features may, for authentication purposes, require you to sign up for other BlackBottom.com services. The privacy notices of those services govern the use of your personal information associated with them.
  * You may update or correct your personal profile information and email preferences at any time by visiting your account profile page.

### Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites

Currently, BlackBottom.com has no relationships with the third-party ad servers or ad networks.

### More Information

For questions concerning our service or your account, please check out the [BlackBottom Help](http://www.blackbottom.com/help.html) page.

For more information about our privacy practices, email or write to us at:

BlackBottom.com Privacy  
8311 Brier Creek Pkwy.  
Suite 105-415  
Raleigh, NC 27617  
USA

313 406-7774 direct  
313 557-0669 fax  
ceo@blackbottom.com
